

# David Obidu

# Software Engineer

I'm an energetic and passionate IT and Business information graduate. I aim to use my knowledge of software, web, and mobile development to satisfy the software engineering position. I have over 6 years of engineering experience and over 3 years of work experience in this field.

daviderinayo@gmail.com

London, United Kingdom

in ng.linkedin.com/in/david-obidu

github.com/zeusmist

+234 8092961769

zeusmist.github.io

@davidobidu

### **SKILLS**

Software development

JavaScript

React JS

React native

Node.js

Firebase / GCP

MongoDB

Python

Flask

C#

Blockchain Development

Web3.js

Ether.js

Solidity

**Smart Contract Auditing** 

Machine Learning Pipeline / Operations

Vertex Al

BigQuery

and more...

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Software Engineer MITA Games

11/2021 - Present Remote (USA)

MITA Games is a Blockchain game studio and creator of Legends Of Mitra, a web3 play-to-earn mobile game, served on BSC & Klaytn blockchain networks. Achievements/Tasks

- □ I built and I'm actively managing the entire frontend of the web3 portal used by over 90k users.
- I integrated the smart contract features on the web3 portal.
- □ I built and I'm actively managing MITA games mobile app used by thousands of users.
- Links: https://mita.games , https://web3.legendsofmitra.com
- Technologies Used: React, Node.js, Solidity, Web3.js, Caver.js, Jekyll, Jest, Capacitor.js, etc...

Contact: Kena - hello@gemslab.io

# Frontend Engineer Stipple (formerly Friyay)

01/2020 - 07/2021

Remote (USA)

A web & mobile app dedicated to helping companies set goals, make plans, work together, and see progress.

Achievements/Tasks

- I built & improved over 30 project management tools used by over 10k businesses serving millions of users worldwide.
- □ The GIDBF tools I created resulted in a major spike in customer growth.
- I contributed to the build of a chat feature which helped the team migrate from Slack.
- Lots of other contributions to the team goals and motivation.
- Links: https://www.stipple.me/
- Technologies Used: React, React Native, Redux, GraphQL, Selenium, Jest, etc.

Contact: Joost Wentink - joost@friyay.io

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Founder / Software Engineer. Off My Chest (OMC)

05/2020 - 11/2021

A mobile app for users to safely express themselves without fear of being judged. Available on all mobile app stores. Achievements/Tasks

- □ I built and improved the entire project from scratch.
- I grew the customer base to a recurring 3k monthly active users.
- □ I gained a deep knowledge of team management, marketing and customer acquisition.
- Links: https://omcmobile.app
- Technologies Used: React Native, React, Firebase / GCP, Node.js, Python, Selenium.

# **EDUCATION**

# (ADSE) Advanced Diploma in Software Engineering Aptech Computer Education

Aptech Computer Education

05/2019 - 09/2021 Lagos

# B.Sc Information Technology and Business Information Systems Middlesex University, London

09/2021 - 09/2022 London

# **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

#### My Online Portfolio (12/2019 - Present)

zeusmist.github.io

### Trystakes (06/2022 - 10/2022)

- A web3 / blockchain social investment game where users create game Stakes for other users to compete.
- https://trystakes.com

### Off My Chest (05/2020 - 11/2021)

available on all mobile app stores

#### Nundio (10/2019)

nundio.herokuapp.com

#### My Company App (12/2019)

mycompanyapp.herokuapp.com

# More on my Github

https://github.com/Zeusmist